ticno.com 2016-11-02

# Ticno Multibar

Download

Version:  
Date:  
Size:  
Requirements: 

Version:  
Date:  
Size:  
Requirements: 

1.1.1.1   
20/08/2011   
13 Mb   
Windows 7/Vista/XP 

1.1.1.1   
20/08/2011   
13 Mb   
Windows 7/Vista/XP 

We respect your privacy. Please read our privacy policy to find out what user information we collect during your usage of the company services and software, how we store and use it. 

##### Privacy policy.

By using the Media Labs Limited (“Company”) software and services (“Services”) you signify the acceptance of the Company Privacy Policy (“Policy”). The Policy applies only to information collected from the Company Services. The Company reserves the right to change the Policy at any time without prior user notice. The changes take effect upon disposal on the Company site (<http://ticno.com/multibar/en/privacy.html>). Your use of the Company Services following the posting of such changes to this Policy will constitute your acceptance of any such changes.

##### Definitions. 

Personally Indentifiable Information (“PII”) – information which can be used to distinguish or trace an individual's identity, such as their name, social security number, biometric records, etc. alone, or when combined with other personal or identifying information which is linked or linkable to a specific individual, such as date and place of birth, mother’s maiden name, etc. 

Cookies - simple pieces of data that can store certain information about your preferences. In privacy purposes your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. They are neither spyware nor viruses and mostly used to improve / modify the website after your preferences. 

##### Collection of Personally identifiable Information.

The Company doesn’t collect any personally identifiable information.

##### Collection of personally non-identifiable information.

With your use of the Company Services we gather certain non-PII information about your web browsing and computer usage, including the following information.

• IP (internet protocol) address  
• browser and operating system information  
• viewed company pages, services and widgets  
• preferences in widgets and services  
• geographic location for weather reports 

This information helps us improve your interaction with the Company Services. On our site we use Google Analytics to track the general behavior of the users. Please refer to Google.com Privacy Policy for more information. 

##### Third party links, services and cookies.

The Company Services may have external links to thirds parties (i.e. other sites). Multibar also allows you to integrate widgets, gadgets and other third party services that are not covered by The Company Policy. Third party services are governed by their own privacy policies. These services have special links leading to the service owner (i.e. Google Gadgets). The Company has no responsibility for the data collection of these sites and services. We encourage you to read legal notices of these sites, including their privacy policies.

##### Security.

We take all reasonable technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect any collected information from damage or loss.
